mvfglobal.com 2017-06-16

# Privacy Policy | MVF

## MVF - Privacy Policy Statement

This Privacy Policy Statement explains the data processing practices of MVF. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact our Privacy Officer by e-mail at [privacy@mvfglobal.com](mailto:privacy@mvfglobal.com).

Registration & Information Collected

We collect personal information from you through the use of enquiry forms and each time you e-mail us your details.  
We also collect information automatically about your visit to our site. This information, which includes demographic data and browsing patterns, is collected via the use of cookies (see below) and session file information.

## Use of personal information

We use personal information collected via MVF to:

* pass on to selected companies only when we have your express permission  
* facilitate communication between yourself and selected partners  
* provide you with a more personalised service

## Use of cookies

We use "cookies" to identify you when you visit the MVF site and to build up a profile of our regular users.  
A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information back from the browser. Our use of cookies also allows members to be presented with a personalised version of the site.  
We will only read cookies from your cookie file placed there through your web browser's interaction with the MVF site. Please see [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/ "www.aboutcookies.org") for more information about cookies.

## Use of session files

We use session files, along with cookies, to log your browsing patterns and so identify the areas of the site which have been of interest to you, allowing us to personalise the MVF site for you.

We also use information in aggregate form (in other words, no individual user is identified) to:

* to build up marketing profiles  
* to allow us to develop the business in ways that help you  
* to manage our relationship with advertisers and  
* to audit usage of the site

All personal, cookie and session ID information are made available to MVF Global employees to enable us and any related third parties to deal more effectively with any enquiry you make.

## Your control over the use of your personal data

You have complete control over the use of your personal information by MVF. You can unsubscribe at any time by emailing [unsubscribe@mvfglobal.com](mailto:unsubscribe@mvfglobal.com)

If it is necessary to transfer your data outside of the EEA, MVF will take all reasonable required steps to ensure that your data and privacy rights continue to be protected

Our site links to other web sites and we are not responsible for the content on those sites or their data policies and procedures.

## Data Protection

MVF is a trading name of Marketing V F Limited. which is registered under the 1998 Data Protection Act, ref PZ1995728.

MVF is committed to the fundamental rights and welfare of our employees, and the employees of our suppliers. As such, we're committed to taking appropriate steps to safeguard our business and supply chain from from modern slavery and human trafficking. For more information, please 

read MVF's UK Modern Slavery Act statement.

## Modern Slavery and Human Trafficking Statement

Marketing VF Limited ( **"MVF" / "we"/ "our"** ) is committed to corporate social responsibility, and to understanding and safeguarding its business and supply chain from modern slavery and human trafficking. MVF is an award-winning company that provides a scalable source of new customers to businesses all over the world. MVF's technology and world-class cross-channel marketing teams help connect active customers with businesses looking to scale. 

We procure different services and products from a number of suppliers.   
The vast majority of our procurement spend is on services, and mainly in the following areas: Online marketing/advertising, IT/cloud-based solutions, and office premises and facilities. Many of the service providers with which we work are large multinational business (e.g. Google, Facebook). Most of the products that we purchase are IT equipment (e.g. laptops, telephones). Again, in the main, we purchase such items from large multinational businesses (e.g. Dell). Given the nature of our business, we believe that the risk of modern slavery or human trafficking in our business or supply chain is very low. This statement is made pursuant to section 54(1) of the Modern Slavery Act 2015. It has been approved by MVF's Board of Directors, and constitutes MVF's modern slavery and human trafficking statement for the financial year ending 31 March 2016. 

**Titus Sharpe  
CEO   
Marketing VF Limited   
23 November 2016 **
